









Summary

As a Junior Frontend Developer, I am proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and frameworks ReactJS. I have experience in creating responsive and user-friendly interfaces that provide an excellent user experience. My focus is on writing clean and maintainable code, attention to detail and problem-solving abilities, collaborating with team members, and continuously improving my skills.

Contact information

(050) 58-48-238 ganna.sarviro@gmail.com <u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u> Kharkiv, Ukraine

Tech skills

HTML5/CSS3/SASS
Responsive design
React/JavaScript
REST API
Material UI, Tailwind CSS
NodeJs, Express
MongoDb, Mongoose
Version control (Git)
Figma
Adobe Illustrator/
Photoshop/InDesign

Soft skills

Eager to learn
Organized
Critical thinking skills
Attention to Detail
Adaptability

Languages

Ukrainian/Russian - Native English - Intermediate

Project experience

- PETLY [LinkFront] [LinkBack]

 React, Redux, NodeJs, Express, MongoDb

 Website where you can post notices for the sale or loss of a pet
- ICE CREAM SHOP [Link]
 [HTML, SASS, JS, Parsel]
 Ice Cream company website with responsible layout
- POISON GAME! [Link]
 [JavaScript, CSS]
 In this game, you need to collect all the necessary ingredients and prepare a poisonous potion!

Work experience

- Freelance
 [2015-2021] Printing
 designificity]posters and brochures
 - design of banners and site logos
 - positive experience in the work remotely
- Kharkiv bearing plant (HARP) [2008-2010] Engineer-technologist of Materials science
 - certified products according to international standard
 - creation of technical documentation

Education

- IT-School Golt, Kyiv [2021-2022]Full Stack Developer
- National Technical Univarsity «Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute», Kharkiv [2002-2008]
 Engineer-technologist of Materials science